A Guide to the Papers of James J. Kilpatrick
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series I: Correspondence
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence - Virginia (Box-folder 52:8)
    Virginia Division-American Cancer Society, Virginia Foundation for Independent Colleges, The Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, Virginia Observer, Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Virginia Press Photographers Association, Virginia Retail Merchants Association, Virginia Safety AssociationVirginia State Chamber of Commerce, Virginia State Bar Association, Virginia State Library, Virginia State Printers Association, Virginia State Restaurant Association, Virginia Transit Company, Virginia Union University, Virginia United Nations Association
  - 1951-1956 Correspondence: Virginia Press Association (Box-folder 52:9)
  - 1955-1957 Correspondence: Virginia Press Association Editorial Seminar-1957 (Box-folder 52:10)
  - 1958-1959 Correspondence: Virginia Press Association Editorial Seminar-1958 (Box-folder 52:11)
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Virginian - End "V" (Box-folder 52:12)
    Virginians for Conservative Government, Richard Viscusi, Mary B. Vogel, Paul W. Vogel-Beacon Fire Insurance Company, H.T. Vogts, Mrs. Donald Volk, Alfred A. Volkmann- The Flat Hat-College of William and Mary, Eula Volmer, Volunteer Service Bureau, Jeanne Vollbrecht Vong, Dorothy Vorse, Clement E. Vose-Bowdoin College, Voting Rights Act, Steve Voyatzis, Henry Vranian
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: W - Wag (Box-folder 53:1)
    WKCR-King's Crown Radio-Columbia University, WLEE Radio, WLES, WRNL, J. Wadas-West Elsdon Pharmacy, G.C. Waddell, S.P. Waddell Jr., Mrs. Addie B. Wade, A.P. Wade Jr., Robert A. Wade, Rev. Will E. Wade, Mrs. Eugene P. Wadsworth, Mrs. Charles B. Wagoner, Evelyn Wagstaff, Sam T. Wagstaff, Samuel Wagstaff, Cy A. Wagner, Margaret Wagner, Rudolph F. Wagner-Richmond Public Schools
  - 1953-1967 Correspondence: Wah - Wal (Box-folder 53:2)
    Ben Wahrman-Reynolds Metals Company, B.C. White, Nancy Woods Walburn, Walter Waldbauer, Dr. George L. and Edith M. Waldbott - National Fluoridation News, Leonard Waldherr, Robert Waldorf-Washington-Lee High School - Western Maryland College, Gayle Waldrop-University of Colorado College of Journalism, Allen H. Walker M.D.-Memphis Convalescent Home, Cecelia K. Walker-Washington County Public Library, Coleman C. Walker, Gen. Edwin A. Walker, George R. Walker-Portsmouth Councilman- Times-Candidate for State Senate, Harry Walker-Mishkan Tefila Forum, John Carter Walker, Lloyd D. Walker, Mary-Belle (Mrs. Joseph R.) Walker, Robert S. Walker III, Ross H. Walker-Abbott Proctor and Paine, Thomas F. Walker, Wall Street Journal
  - 1954-1965 Correspondence: J. Barrye Wall- The Farmville Herald (Box-folder 53:3)
  - 1956-1967 Correspondence: Wall - Walt (Box-folder 53:4)
    C.H. Wallace, George C. Wallace-Alabama Governor, Mrs. George C. Wallace Sr., George R. Wallace, Maj. Gen. M.M. Wallace-USAR (ret.), Mary Wallace, Raymond B. Wallace Jr.- The Tiger-Hampden-Sydney College, Stanley Wallant Jr., Frank W. Waller, Thomas K. Waller, C. Lamar Wallis-Richmond Public Library, I.H. Wallmeyer, John J. Wallo Sr., Bernice Wallus, James Walsh, Walter W. Walsh Jr., Dan E. Walter, Hon. Francis E. Walter M.C. House of Representatives-15 th District Pennsylvania, William J. Walter, Pauline Walter Alice Walton Mr. and Mrs. B.F. Walton - Superintendent of Schools-Lawrenceville Virginia, Mrs. C.C. Walton Jr., L.E. Walton, Naomi Walton, W. Robert Walton-Allen-Scott Column
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Wam - Was (Box-folder 53:5)
    William C. Wampler, A. Ward, Caroline Ward, Carlyle Ward- The Mobile Register, R. Dulaney Ward Jr., Robert W. Ward-Florida Cypress Gardens, William M. Ward DDS, Mrs. Trophie Warder, Georgia Dickinson (Mrs. J. Powell) Wardlaw - Daughters of the American Revolution, C. Arthur Ware, Ralph M. Ware Jr.-Virginia Board of Pharmacy, Dabney T. Waring, Gerald P. Waring -The Richmond Virginians Baseball, Thomas R. Waring- The Charleston News and Courier, Dr. Charles E. Warnell-Mt. Tabor Clinic, Charles Willard H. Warner, Leonard Warner-American Farm Bureau Federation, Joe Warren, Miss Warren, R.L. Warren, W.R. Warren Jr., Washington and Lee University, William K. Warriner
  - 1954-1966 Correspondence: Wat - Webe (Box-folder 53:6)
    James K. Waters, Kelso Waters-Harding College, Mrs. B.C. Watkins Sr., E.D. Watkins, George E. Watkins-Grove Avenue Baptist Church, Irvine C. Watkins, James S. Watkinson-Morton G. Thalhimer Inc., Lois D. Watkins- The Hanover Herald Progress, P.R. Watkins, W.T. Watkins-Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, William R. Watkins MD-South Boston Clinic, James E. Watlington Jr., Rev. Paul B. Watlington Jr.-Orange Baptist Church, George M. Watson Jr., William C. Watt, A.A. Watters Jr., L.L. Watts-Virginia Association of Workers for the Blind, Lavaida Watts, Mrs. Thomas E. Watts, Mrs. G.J. Watumull-Citizens' Pure Water Committee, Mrs. G. Bourne (Norma A.) Wayland, Edward A. Payne-Federal Reserve Bank of Richmond, Carolyn D. Weaver, G. Park Weaver, M.A. Weaver Jr., Richard M. Weaver- Modern Age, Bertha Webb-T.S. Cooley Elementary School, Charles A. Webb-Assistant to John W. Bricker-U.S. Senate -Ohio, David Webb- Lawyers Title News, James W. Webb, Susan Webb, Brent Webber, E.W. Webber-College of William and Mary Department of Government, L. Webber, Louis C. Weber, Paul A. Weber
  - 1956-1967 Correspondence: Webs - Wei (Box-folder 53:7)
    Barbara S. Webster-Public Opinion Surveys, Bethuel M. Webster, Howard H. Webster-McGarvey-Genealogical Research, Herbert Wechsler, Robert Weed, Elie Weeks-Rochambeau Farm, Ross Weeks Jr. -Richmond SDX, John Weichold, C. Maurice Weidemeyer-House of Delegates-Maryland, M.Sgt. Kent Weidleik, Sadie Weidra, Weil Gotshal and Manges, Mrs. Morton Weiman, Morton Weinberg, F.C. Weirich, George M. Weiss, Mrs. M. Herbert Weiss, Steve Weissman - Cornell University, Faye Weitinger
  - 1956-1967 Correspondence - Wel (Box-folder 53:8)
    N.S. Welch Jr., Robert H.W. Welch Jr.-John Birch Society, George Weller- The Chicago Daily News - Rome Bureau, Donald Sultner Welles, Jack Wellington, Benjamin Wells, Dr. Harold Scott Wells, June Wells, Kenneth D. Wells-Freedoms Foundation at Valley Forge, Luther Coleman Wells, Luther W. Wells, R.L. Wells, Sheldon S. Wells, Mr. and Mrs. V.L. Wells, W.D. Wells, John B. Welsh, Douglas Welson-Drew University, Irving C. Welsted, Courtney Welton, David Welton-Medical Society of the State of North Carolina
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Wen - Wey (Box-folder 54:1)
    George B. Wendell Jr.-Trinity College, Erik Wensberg, C. Frank Wentzel Jr., William M. Werber, G. Wise Wescott-Automobile Club of Virginia, Thomas J. Wesley Jr., John Wessells-State Department of Agriculture, Frank Wessely, Lola W. Wesson, Charles B. West, Francis West, Fray M. West Jr., Rose Marie West, Shirley Jean West, R.L. Westbrook, Clifford P. Westermeier-University of Arkansas, Alan F. Westin-Columbia University, Albert H. Wetzel, Frank Wetzel, John C. Wetzel, John H. Wetzel, Harry F. Weyher
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Wha - Whe (Box-folder 54:2)
    Richard Whalen- Fortune, Mr. and Mrs. James C. Wheat, Dr. Thomas Foster Wheeldon, D.B. Wheeler, Dr. Raymond M. Wheeler-Charlotte Medical Clinic, Richard S. Wheeler - Rally, Timothy J. Wheeler - Rally, H. Joseph Wheelhouse #74157-Virginia State Penitentiary, Everett L. Whenham (California Jack)-Skyway Records
  - 1956-1967 Correspondence - Whit (Box-folder 54:3)
    Dr. L.D. "Doc" Whitaker, Mildred P. Whitaker, Anne White, Mrs. Charles J. White, E.B. White- The New Yorker, Mrs. Frank E. (Edna R.) White, George B. White, Gerald H. White, Hugh V. White-Superintendent-Nansemond County Schools, Hugh V. White Jr., J. Stuart White-Commission on Conservation and Development, Jack White-New York Yankee (letterhead), James F. White, Jane White, John Ellington White - University of Richmond, John F. White-National Educational Television, John G. White, John J. White-Richmond Virginians Baseball, John R. White, La Verna White, M.O. White, N.G. "Jack" White-White System Company, R.E. White-Winchester Volunteer Rescue Squad, Richard G. White, Col. Robert Harvey White, Robert M. White III- New York Herald Tribune, Mrs. W.N. White, Warren T. White, William E. White Jr.-Henrico County Public Schools, William H. White Jr.-University of Virginia, William M. White Jr.
  - 1956-1967 Correspondence: Whitecotton -Whitmire (Box-folder 54:4)
    N.L. Whitecotton-General Electric Company, Mrs. Douglas J. Whitehead-Daughters of the American Revolution, Ed Whitehead - WRVA Radio, Lollie C. Whitehead-Virginia Department of Law, Donald S. Whiteheart, Dick Whitehurst, Chris Whiteman III- Harrisburg Baksheesh, Irene Whiteneck, A.G. Whitener- High Point Daily News, A.E. Whitesell, Louis B. Whitfield Jr.-Alaga Syrup Company-Whitfield Pickle Company, Rev. Samuel B. Whitfield - Westside Baptist Church, Robert Whitford, John M. Whiting, Donald P. Whitley-Francis I. DuPont and Company, Tyler Whitley, C. Glenn Whitlock, E.S. Whitlock-WRNL, Jewel S. Whitlock, Kenneth Whitlock, Scott Whitlock, W.W. Whitlock, Bert Whitman, Hon. George P. Whitman Sr.-Atlanta Judicial Circuit Court, R. Lee Whitmire
  - 1952-1960 Correspondence: Robert Whitehead (Box-folder 54:5)
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Whitney - Whitten (Box-folder 54:6)
    L.E. Whitney-The Whitney Company, Leila Whitney, Lloyd Whitney, Natalie F. Whitney-Virginia State Society-Descendants of the Signers of the Declaration of Independence, Capt. Richard T. Whitney USNR (ret.), O.H. Whitten
  - 1955-1965 Correspondence: Who - Wid (Box-folder 54:7)
    Who's Who, Mr. and Mrs. James L. Wick - Human Events, Milton I. Wick, J. Caldwell Wicker-Fork Union Military Academy, Tome Wicker- The New York Times, Alice Widener - USA Magazine, H.Emory Widener, Mary M. Widener-Republican Congressional Committee-The Kiplinger Washington Editors Inc., Ralph W. Widener Jr.-Sones of Confederate Veterans, Albert J. Widmer
  - 1954-1964 Correspondence: John J. Wicker Jr. (Box-folder 54:8)
  - 1953-1965 Correspondence: Wilb - Wilh (Box-folder 54:9)
    Marcia G. Wilber, Vincent P. Wilber-Division of Public Liaison - Department of State, Barbara Wilbur, Paula Wilcox, Thomas Wilcox, Austin Wilder, E.F.W. Wildermuth, Charles W. Wiley, Evelyn U. Wiles, H.F. Wiley-City of College Park, John J. Wilhelm, A.L. Wilhoite
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Wilkerson - I. Wilkinson (Box-folder 55:1)
    Albert C. Wilkerson, T.L. Wilkerson, Woodrow W. Wilkerson-State Board of Education, Gilbert Wilkes, Judge Robert N. Wilkin-U.S. District Court, Roy Wilkins-NAACP, Byron M. Wilkinson-Hatcher Memorial Baptist Church, Dan Wilkinson-Neighborhood Theatres, Mrs. E.P. Wilkinson, Elizabeth Wilkinson, Ernest L. Wilkinson, Mrs. H.W. Wilkinson, Isham T. Wilkinson
  - 1956-1967 Correspondence: J. Wilkinson-Willey (Box-folder 55:2)
    J. Harvie Wilkinson Jr.-State Planters' Bank, J. Harvie Wilkinson III-Yale Political Union, James B. Wilkinson-Commonwealth's Attorney, Leonard H. Wilkinson, T.D. Wilkinson Jr., W. Scott Wilkinson, Erwin H. Will-Virginia Electric and Power Company, Clyde H. Willard, Henry I. Willett-Superintendent of Richmond Public Schools, A.E. Willey, C.R. Willey-State Entomologist - Department of Agriculture and Immigration, Sen. Edward E. Willey - 34 th District-Richmond City
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: William and Mary-J. Williams (Box-folder 55:3)
    College of William and Mary, A. Simpson Williams Jr., Abigail Williams, Anthony Williams, Berkely Williams, Mrs. C. Ernest Williams, C.L. Williams, Carey Williams- The Herald-Journal, Dr. Carrington Williams, Celine and Alex Williams, Charles P. Williams-Washington National Insurance Company- The National Program Letter, Cranston Williams, Don Williams, E.F. Williams, E.O.N. Williams-Northwest Sports Attractions, Fred C. Williams, Mrs. Frederick W. Williams, George Washington Williams, Gerard S. Williams, Mrs. Grant Williams-State Bar of Georgia, Harley M. Williams-Virginia Citizens Committee for Better Schools, Harry M. Williams Jr.-Maggie L. Walker High School, Irene Williams, J.C. Williams, J.H. Williams Jr., J. Mack Williams, James A. Williams - Southwest Virginia Enterprise, Jane Williams, Mrs. Richard Douglass Williams Jr., Janie T. Williams, Joe Williams, John Bell Williams (Kilpatrick's neighbor), John J. Williams-U.S. Senate-Deleware, John Page Williams - Church Schools in the Diocese of Virginia, John R. Williams-News Publishing Company, Hon. Joseph J. Williams Jr.-Attorney General of Texas
  - 1955-1966 Correspondence: J. Harvie Williams-American Good Government Society-Alexander Hamilton Bicentennial Commission (Box-folder 55:4)
  - 1954-1966 Correspondence: L. Williams -W. Williams (Box-folder 55:5)
    Langbourne M. Williams-Freeport Sulpher Company, Lewis C. Williams, Lou Williams, Dr. Louis H. Williams, Mrs. Mattie Williams, Murat Williams, Norman L. Williams, O.L. Williams, Oliver Williams, Mrs. R. Douglass Williams Jr.-Virginia State Symphony Orchestra and Opera Company, Randolph C. Williams-Williams Printing Company, Richard A. Williams, Robert F. Williams-Virginia Education Association, Robert H. Williams-Williams Publications, S. Carter Williams, S. Howe Williams, T.V. Williams Jr., Thomoas L. Williams, W. Reid Williams Jr.-Pine Top Poultry Farm, Walton L. Williams, Wilton P. Williams, Wirt Williams-Los Angeles State College
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence - Williamsburg-Q. Wilson (Box-folder 55:6)
    Colonial Williamsburg, Elizabeth Williamson, L.M. Williamson, Pamela S. Williamson, Walter H. Williamson "Culture under Communism", Mrs. L. Isalun Willis, Ruth H. Willoughby, Garry Willis, Mrs. William Kenneth Wills, S.D. Willson-Top Value Enterprises, Mrs. W.B. Wilmore, Mrs. Alvin M. Wilson, Dr. Archer A. Wilson M.D., Aubrey Wilson, Mrs. Charles Harrison Wilson, Charles P. Wilson-C & W Control Company, Hon. Earl Wilson-U.S. Congress, Eugene E. Wilson, Mr. and Mrs. Fielding L. Wilson, George P. Wilson-American Dialect Society, Mrs. Jean Haley Wilson, John D. Wilson, John R. Wilson Jr. -Washington and Lee University, Kieth Wilson- Omaha World Herald, Leonard R. Wilson - University of Alabama, Lyle C. Wilson-United Press International, Margaret M. Wilson, Quintus C. Wilson-West Virginia University School of Journalism
  - 1953-1967 Correspondence: R. Wilson - Wir (Box-folder 55:7)
    R.B. Wilson-Armstrong High School, Robert Archer Wilson, Victor P. Wilson, S.F.C. William Wilson-HQ B Co. 27 th Ordinance Battalion, Winchester Evening Star, John Henry Winder (Subject), Ralph B. Winders-Mississippi Baptist Convention Board, E.E. Windes, Mrs. J.T. Windham-Fidelia Club, Jean Windmiller, B.D. Winfield Jr., R. Westwood Winfree-Richmond Artists Association, Harvey N. Wingfield Jr.-Richmond Area Protective Council, John K. Winkler, William W. Winkler, Billie Winn, C. Edgar Winn, Hawthorne Winner, Lawrence L. Winship- The Boston Globe, Joseph E. Winslow-The White House, James Winston, Edward H. Winter-University of Virginia Department of Sociology and Anthropology, John S. Winter-Minneapolis-Honeywell Regulator Company, Thomas S. Winter- Human Events, A.R. Winters, Mrs. E. Ray Winters, Glenn R. Winters- Journal of the American Judicature Society, Leonard Wirkus-Union County Open Forum, William C. Wirth
  - 1949-1966 Correspondence: Wis - Wom (Box-folder 55:8)
    Henry A. Wise, J. Hooper Wise, Jack Dana Wise, Col. Jennings C. Wise, Julian S. Wise-Southern Oxygen Company, G.G. Wisland, Worth R. Wiswall, Marion I. Witheridge, Virginia Withers, Shepherd L. Witman -Residential Seminars on World Affairs-Lafayette College, Richard Tucker Witt, Walter F. Witt-Virginia Restaurant Association, Mrs. Murray Forbes Wittichen-United Daughters of the Confederacy, L.D. Wittkower Sr., F.J. Wittman, Hoyt Wofford, Willard L. Wolcott, Jack Wolf-Gallery of Modern Art, New York, Lloyd H. Wolf, Arthur L. Wolfe-International Science Service, Dinah Wolfe, Richard C. Wolfe, William H. Wolfe, S.A. Wolff, Raymond E. Wolfinger-The Brookings Institute, F.H. Womack
  - 1950-1967 Correspondence: Wood - Wor (Box-folder 56:1)
    Ann C. Wood, Art Wood-Cartoonist, James F. Wood, Dr. John E. Wood, Gen. John Elliott Wood, Keith S. Wood, Lucy H. Wood, Robert F. Wood, Ruth T. Wood, Thatcher S. Wood, William Thomas Wood, Mrs. Wyatt C. Wood Jr., R.L. Woodall, Mr. and Mrs. James D. Woodard Jr., D.W. Woodbridge, Wayne Woodlief, Robert J. Woodruff- Montano Magazine, Mrs. William S.D. (Page) Woods, Charles S. Woodson Jr.-State Police, Mrs. Frederick A. Woodson Jr., John E. Woodward Jr., R.L. Woodward Jr., William C. Wooldridge- The Harvard Conservative, John Woolfolk, Mark H. Woolsey- United States Law Week, Hugh H. Wooten, Paul Worden, Mrs. R. Workman, William D. Workman Jr.- The State, World Book Company, World Fellowship of Religions, René Wormser, Mrs. Frank A. Worrell, T. Eugene Worrell-Bristol Newspaper Printing, Ralph P. Worthington
  - 1953-1954 Correspondence: John Cook Wyllie (Box-folder 56:2)
  - 1955 Correspondence: John Cook Wyllie (Box-folder 56:3)
  - 1956-1957 Correspondence: John Cook Wyllie (Box-folder 56:4)
  - 1958-1959 Correspondence: John Cook Wyllie (Box-folder 56:5)
  - 1960-1967 Correspondence: John Cook Wyllie (Box-folder 56:6)
  - 1954-1967 Correspondence: Wra-End "W" (Box-folder 56:7)
    William H. (Bill) Wranek-University of Virginia Hospital - University News Service, Will Wright, Charles Alan Wright - University of Texas School of Law, David Wright, Douglas B. Wright, Mrs. E. O. Wright-Wright's Grocery, Col. E. Vernon Wright, Erminie King Wright, George Wright III-Virginia Manufacturers Association, H. Franklin Wright, H.T. Wright, Mrs. Helen H. Wright, John H. Wright-King Features Syndicate, Major John Wright-Chief of Detectives-Bureau of Police-Chief of Police, Marcellus Wright Jr.-Architect-City Planning Commission, Porter C. Wright, Suzanne Wright, Thomas Wright, William A. Wright, Mrs. Samuel S. Wurtzel-Jewish Welfare Fund, Edward A. Wyatt IV- The Progress-Index, Louis C. Wyman, John Wyne-Asheville Citizen-Times Publishing Company, Edward J. Wynne Jr. New York University, Mrs. H.R. Wyrick, R.J. Wysor
  - 1955-1967 Correspondence: X-C. Young (Box-folder 57:1)
    John Xifos, Igor Yacenko, Preston M. Yancey, Stanley Yankus, Robert M. Yarbrough, Jr.-Christchurch School, Adam Yarmolinski-Special Assistant to the Secretary of Defense, Moss W. Yater-Florida College, Capt. Virginia F. Yates-USAF, William R. Yates, J.B. Yeabower, F.W. Yeager, Earl L. Yeakel MD-Austin Anesthesiology Group, E. James Wiley-Yellow Cab Company of Virginia, David N. Yerkes, Edwin M. Yoder Jr.- Greensboro Daily News, Will Yolen-Overseas Press Club of America, Maj. Rice M. Youell-Division of Corrections, Young Americans for Freedom, Young Republicans Club-Rockford College, A.C. Young III - E.M. Todd Company, Alieda Young, Aubrey D. Young, Bernie E. Young - Southern Railway System, Dr. Charles A. Young Jr.
  - 1955-1965 Correspondence: E. Young - End "Y" (Box-folder 57:2)
    Edgar Young, Frank L. Young, Glenn O. Young, Harold N. Young - Virginia Polytechnic Institute-Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, Dr. Harry H. Young, Henry C. Young-Cactus Petroleum, James A. Young, James H. Young-Sheriff, James R. Young- Anderson Independent-Tribune, Joseph S. Young, Leslie M. Young, Victoria Young-Defenders of State Sovereignty, W.W. Young-Overnite Transportation Company, William A. Youngblood, Lee Younger-State Corporation Commission, John Yunaites
  - 1955-1965 Correspondence - Z (Box-folder 57:3)
    Alfred F. Zachry-Walter F. George School of Law-Mercer University, C.N. Zapantis, Anne P. Zardles, Joyce Zasorin, Mrs. Paul Zehngraff, Carl Zeitz, Olga Zembrzycki, Mrs. Henry Zendle, Dick Zenk, John M. Ziegler, Walt Thomas Zielinski, Linda Zimmerman, James R. Zinck, Mr. and Mrs. Reno M. Zinzarella, Mr. and Mrs. Michael Zodun, David R. Zukerman-Vanderbilt University, Bert L. Zuver - Des Moines City Assessor-National Association of Assessing Officers, John P. Zvetina, Rudy E. Zydemens
- Series II: Editorials and Editorial Materials
  - 1950-1954, n.d. Dr. Douglas S. Freeman (Box-folder 58:1)
  - 1953 Dr. Douglas S. Freeman - Condolences (Box-folder 58:2)
  - 1953 Jan-Apr Forum-Books and Book Reviews-John Cook Wyllie (Box-folder 58:3)
  - 1953 May-Dec Forum-Books and Book Reviews-John Cook Wyllie (Box-folder 58:4)
  - n.d. Forum-Editorials - Unused (Box-folder 58:5)
  - 1942-1943, 1951 Forum-FBI, etc. (Box-folder 58:6)
  - 1948-1953, n.d. Forum-Phoney Name Letters (Box-folder 58:7)
  - 1955 Interposition-Editorials - Complete Set-November 21, 1955-September 14, 1956 (Box-folder 58:8)
  - 1955 Interposition-Editorials - 1 st Reprints (Box-folder 58:9)
  - 1955 Interposition - Tearsheets (Box-folder 58:10)
  - 1960 Margaret Wagner-Letters to Kilpatrick (Box-folder 58:11)
  - 1960 Margaret Wagner-Letters to Virginius Dabney (Box-folder 58:12)
  - 1960 Margaret Wagner File (Box-folder 58:13)
  - 1960 Margaret Wagner File (Box-folder 59:1)
  - 1960 Margaret Wagner File (Box-folder 59:2)
  - 1960 Margaret Wagner File (Box-folder 59:3)
  - 1960 Margaret Wagner File (Box-folder 59:4)
  - 1960 Margaret Wagner File (Box-folder 59:5)
  - 1960 Margaret Wagner File (Box-folder 59:6)
  - 1953-1957 National Conference of Editorial Writers (Box-folder 59:7)
  - 1951 National Conference of Editorial Writers-1951-North Carolina (Box-folder 59:8)
  - 1954 National Conference of Editorial Writers-Analysis and Critique (Box-folder 59:9)
  - 1951-1956 National Conference of Editorial Writers- Masthead (Box-folder 59:10)
  - 1955-1956 National Conference of Editorial Writers-Members A-G (Box-folder 60:1)
  - 1955-1956 National Conference of Editorial Writers-Members H-Z (Box-folder 60:2)
  - 1954-1955 National Conference of Editorial Writers-Washington Meeting (Box-folder 60:3)
  - 1955-1956 National Conference of Editorial Writers-1955-Minutes and Correspondence (Box-folder 60:4)
  - 1956 National Conference of Editorial Writers-1956-Minneapolis Meeting (Box-folder 60:5)
  - 1956 National Conference of Editorial Writers-Site Committee (Box-folder 60:6)
  - 1955-1956 National Conference of Editorial Writers-Treasury (Box-folder 60:7)
  - 1956 National Conference of Editorial Writers-1956 (Box-folder 60:8)
  - 1956 National Conference of Editorial Writers-Washington Meeting (Box-folder 60:9)
  - 1957 National Conference of Editorial Writers-Oklahoma City Meeting (Box-folder 60:10)
  - 1958 National Conference of Editorial Writers-Philadelphia Meeting (Box-folder 60:11)
  - 1959 National Conference of Editorial Writers-1960 (1959 material) (Box-folder 60:12)
  - 1959-1960 National Conference of Editorial Writers-1960 Minutes, Constitution, and other not directly related to the 1960 Convention (Box-folder 60:13)
  - 1958-1960, Sep National Conference of Editorial Writers-1960-Correspondence and Supplementary Materials (Box-folder 60:14)
  - 1960-1961 National Conference of Editorial Writers-1960-Correspondence and Supplementary Material (Box-folder 61:1)
  - 1960-1961 National Conference of Editorial Writers-1960-Thursday (Box-folder 61:2)
  - 1960-1961 National Conference of Editorial Writers-1960-Friday (Box-folder 61:3)
  - 1960-1961 National Convention of Editorial Writers-1960-Friday Speeches (Box-folder 61:4)
  - 1959-1960 National Conference of Editorial Writers-1960-Saturday (Box-folder 61:5)
  - 1960 National Conference of Editorial Writers-Thank You Notes and Bills (Box-folder 61:6)
  - 1960 National Conference of Editorial Writers-1960-Treasurer's Reports (Box-folder 61:7)
  - 1960 National Conference of Editorial Writers-1960-Transcripts (Box-folder 61:8)
  - 1951 Richmond Newspapers Booklet (Box-folder 61:9)
  - 1951, Jan 23 Richmond Newspapers Booklet - The Washington Post-The Making of the Washington Post (Box-folder 61:10)
  - 1955 Apr-Dec 15 Right of Interposition (Box-folder 61:11)
  - 1955 Dec 15-28 Right of Interposition (Box-folder 61:12)